[
  {
    "question": "Abdominal Pains / Problems",
    "answer": "ABDO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Allergies / Envenomations (Stings/Bites)",
    "answer": "ALLE",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Animal Bites / Attacks",
    "answer": "ANIB",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Back Pain",
    "answer": "BACK",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Breathing Problems",
    "answer": "BREA",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Burns (Scalds) / Explosion (Blast)",
    "answer": "BURN",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Carbon Monoxide / Inhalation / HAZMAT",
    "answer": "CARBMO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cardiac or Respiratory Arrest / Death",
    "answer": "CARD",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chest Pain / Chest Discomfort",
    "answer": "CHEST",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chocking",
    "answer": "CHOK",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convulsions / Seizures",
    "answer": "CONV",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Diabetic Problems",
    "answer": "DIAB",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drowning",
    "answer": "DROWN",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrocution / Lightning",
    "answer": "ELEC",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Eye Problems / Injuries",
    "answer": "EYEP",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Falls",
    "answer": "FALLS",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Headache",
    "answer": "HEAD",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heart Problems / A.I.C.D.",
    "answer": "HEPR",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heat / Cold Exposure",
    "answer": "HECO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hemorrhage (Bleeding) / Lacerations",
    "answer": "HEMO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Overdose / Poisoning (Ingestion)",
    "answer": "OVER",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pregnancy / Childbirth / Miscarriage",
    "answer": "PREG",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sick Person (Specific Diagnosis)",
    "answer": "SICK",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Impalement / Penetrating Trauma",
    "answer": "IMPALE",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Self-Inflicted GSW / Stab",
    "answer": "STABSI",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stroke / Transient Ischemic Attack (TIA)",
    "answer": "STROKE",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traffic Collision / Transportation Incident (with Injury)",
    "answer": "MVCPI",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traumatic Injuries (Specific)",
    "answer": "TRAU",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unconscious / Fainting (Near)",
    "answer": "UNCO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transfer / Interfacility / Palliative Care",
    "answer": "TIPC",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aircraft Emergency",
    "answer": "AIRC",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alarms",
    "answer": "ALARFI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Citizen Assist / Service Call",
    "answer": "FIASST",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Confined Space / Structure Collapse",
    "answer": "CONFSP",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrical Hazard",
    "answer": "ELEHAZ",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Elevator / Escalator Rescue",
    "answer": "ELEVATR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explosion",
    "answer": "EXPLOS",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Extrication / Entrapped (Machinery, Vehicle - Non MVC",
    "answer": "ENTRAP",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fuel Spill / Fuel Odor",
    "answer": "FUELSP",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gas Leak / Gas Odor (Natural or LP Gas)",
    "answer": "GASLEA",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "HAZMAT",
    "answer": "HAZM",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "High Angle Rescue (Above or Below Grade)",
    "answer": "HIANGL",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lightning Strike (Investigation)",
    "answer": "LIGHTN",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marine Fire / Boat Fire",
    "answer": "BOATFI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mutual Aid / Assist Outside Agency",
    "answer": "MUTF",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Odor (Strange / Unknown)",
    "answer": "ODORIN",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Outside Fire",
    "answer": "OUTFIR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Smoke Investigation (Outside)",
    "answer": "SMOINV",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Structure Fire",
    "answer": "STRUCT",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Train and Rail Collision / Derailment",
    "answer": "TRAINC",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vehicle Fire",
    "answer": "VEHI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Water / Ice / Mud Rescue",
    "answer": "WATRES",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Watercraft in Distress / Collision",
    "answer": "WATERC",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Train and Rail Fire",
    "answer": "TRAINF",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motor Vehicle Collision",
    "answer": "MVCFI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Outside Tank Fire (Use 67)",
    "answer": "OUTFIR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sinking Vehicle / Vehicle in Floodwater",
    "answer": "WATRES",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vegetation / Wildland / Brush / Grass Fire (Use 67)",
    "answer": "OUTFIR",
    "category": "EFD"
  }
]
